Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Source Material
  - Subseries B: By Subject
    - Wind, Jane, undated (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - The Winds, undated (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Clippings
  Series VI: Clippings contains articles clipped from newspapers, magazines and other published materials, some to be used as research material, others for documentation purposes.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by title. Items within each folder are in their original order, with the exception of the “general clippings” file, in which articles have been arranged chronologically within each folder. Any titles inferred by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
  A facsimile of the following book was separated from this series and deaccessioned:
  Adams, Henry. History of the United States During the First Administration of Thomas Jefferson, Vol. II. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1921.
  - Art (1 of 2), 1965-2002, undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Art (2 of 2), 1965-2002, undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Articles of Interest (1 of 2), 1984-2001, undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Articles of Interest (2 of 2), 1984-2001, undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Articles on Others (Not L.R.), 1969-93, undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Bradley, Bill (1 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Bradley, Bill (2 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Bradley, Bill (3 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Caracas Exhibition, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Exhibition Announcements & Invitation Cards (1 of 2), 1968-98, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements & Invitation Cards (2 of 2), 1968-98, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Fashion, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Ferro, Pablo, 1983-2000, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - French Press Clippings, 1977-1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - General Clippings, 1949-1965 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - General Clippings, 1965-1969 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - General Clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - General Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - General Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - General Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - General Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - General Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - General Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - General Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - General Clippings, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - General Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - General Clippings, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - General Clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - General Clippings, 1998-2000 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - General Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - General Clippings, 2000-2008 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - General Clippings, undated (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - General Clippings, undated (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - General Clippings, undated (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - German Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - German Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - History of Matzah: The Story of the Jews, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Homosexuality, 1993-95 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - "In Memory of My Feelings: Frank O'Hara and American Art" at Parrish Art Museum, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    The following book was removed from the archive and cataloged in the Fales book collections:
    O'Hara, Frank. What's with Modern Art? Bill Berkson, ed. Austin, Texas: Mike and Dale's Press, 1999.
  - Italian Press Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Jewish People (1 of 2), 1981-2000, undated (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Jewish People (2 of 2), 1981-2000, undated (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Kestner-Gesellschaft Retrospektive, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - "Larry Rivers: The Master's Eye" Exhibition at Robert Kidd Gallery, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Law-related Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Law-related Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Legere, Phoebe, 1985-1999 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Lonesome Traveler, by Jack Kerouac (review inscribed to Rivers by Kerouac), 1960 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Marlborough Exhibition, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Marlborough (Santiago, Chile) Exhibition, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (include literature), 1976-2002, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 4), 1961-97, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 4), 1961-97, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (3 of 4), 1961-97, undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (4 of 4), 1961-97, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Music, 1978-79, undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Musicians etc., 1972-85, undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Nudes (1 of 2), 1964-68, undated (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Nudes (2 of 2), 1964-68, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Personal Clippings, 1961-2000 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Reviews - Other Artists / Poets, 1983-98, undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Reviews - Rivers, 1951-1989 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Reviews - Rivers, 1990-97, undated (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Rivers's Obituary in Artforum, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Russia Trip, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - "Sensation" exhibition at Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - "Special Interest Newspaper & Magazine Articles", 1999-2001, undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - "The Suicide" by Nikolai Erdman, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - "Texas v. Johnson" Case, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Vega, Suzanne, 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - What Did I Do? (1 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - What Did I Do? (2 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - What Did I Do? (3 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Series VII: Music
  Series VII: Music contains materials related to Rivers’ musical career, including sheet music, correspondence and ephemera related to different bands and musical performances.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by file title. Items within each folder are in their original order. Any titles inferred by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
  - Brofsky, Howard, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Climax Band, 1992-99, undated (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Climax Band - Contracts, 1990-1997 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1996 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - East Thirteenth Street Band, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Engagements, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Foss, Lukas, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    Translation of "Story of a Soldier," inscribed to Rivers by Lukas Foss.
  - Hat, Lenny: History 1 on 1 / Rain for the Heat, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Lyric Sheets, undated (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - The Music Festival of the Hamptons, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Performance Press, Flyers, Posters and Invitations, 1985-90, undated (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Performance Press, Flyers, Posters and Invitations, 1999-2001, undated (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Printed Sheet Music (Box 79)
    The following titles comprise Larry Rivers' collection of printed sheet music:
    “The II-V7-I Progression”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “13 Favorite Standards”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “17 All-Time Standards”, Volume 25, by Jamey Aebersold, for Instrumentalists & Vocalists
    “28 Kompositioner”, by Lars Jansson
    “All ‘Bird’: Ten Bebop Jazz Originals by Charlie Parker”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “All of Me”, by Seymour Simons & Gerald Marks
    “Alone Together”, Words & Music by Howard Dietz & Arthur Schwartz
    “And I Love Her”, Words & Music by John Lennon & Paul McCartney, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Anthology of French Song”, Collected & Edited by Max Spicker
    “The Artistry of John Coltrane”
    “As Time Goes By”, Words & Music by Herman Hupfeld
    “Ballads”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “The Best of the Bossa Novas”, by Antonio Carlos Jobim
    “The Best Jazz Standards Ever”, for Piano, Vocal, & Guitar
    “Blueberry Hill”, Music & Lyrics by Al Lewis, Larry Stock & Vincent Rose, for Piano/Vocal
    “Bluer Than Blue”, Composed & Arranged by Ernie Wilkins
    “Bossa Nova”, Volume 31, by Jamey Aebersold, for Instrumentalists & Vocalists
    “Boulevard of Broken Dreams”, Words by Al Dubin, Music by Harry Warren
    “Brother Bill”, Words & Music by Louis Armstrong
    “Bublitchki: Baigelach, Koift Heisenke Baigelach”, by Ziggie Elman, for Voice & Piano
    “Bye Bye Blackbird”, Lyrics by Mort Dixon, Music by Ray Henderson
    “Cabaret”, Words by Fred Ebb, Music by John K&er, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Calypso Tune”, Composed & Arranged by Marshall Brown
    “I Can’t Get Started”, Lyrics by Ira Gershwin, Music by Vernon Duke, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Charlie Parker Omnibook”, for C Instruments
    “Classics Go Latin”, by Irving Fields, for Piano
    “Combo-Orks for Small Dance B&s”, Arranged by Paul Hill, for Trumpet, Clarinet, Tenor Sax
    “Curriculum Vitae”, by Lukas Foss, for Solo Accordion
    “Duke Ellington: Nine Greatest Hits”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “Enseignement du Saxophone par Marcel Mule: Cinquante Trois Etudes”, by Alphonse Leduc
    “Enseignement du Saxophone par Marcel Mule: Dix Huit Exercices ou Etudes”, by Alphonse Leduc
    “Enseignement du Saxophone par Marcel Mule: Etudes Variees”, by Alphonse Leduc
    “Enseignement du Saxophone par Marcel Mule: Exercices Journaliers”, by Alphonse Leduc
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for Drums
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for 1st Alto Sax
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for 1st Tenor Sax
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for 1st Trombone
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for 1st Trumpet
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for Guitar
    “Exciting Sounds of the Big Band Era”, for Piano-Conductor
    “Fame”, Lyrics by Dean Pitchford, Music by Michael Gore
    “Famous Song Hits”, Book 2, Arranged by Elmer Ihrke, for Hammond Chord Organ
    “Famous Transcribed Recorded Jazz Solos: Charlie ‘Bird’ Parker”, Transcribed by W. Dorsey Stuart, for All Instruments
    “Fly Me to the Moon (In Other Words)”, by Bart Howard
    “Georgia on My Mind”, Music by Hoagy Carmichael, Lyrics by Stuart Gorrell, for Piano
    “The Girl from Ipanema”, Music by Antonio Carlos Jobim, English Words by Norman Gimbel, Original Words by Vinicus de Moraes, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “The Girl From Ipanema”, Music by Antonio Carlos Jobim, English Words by Norman Gimbel, Original Words by Vinicus De Moraes
    “Goodnight My Love”, Words & Music by Mack Gordon & Harry Revel
    “The Great Music of Duke Ellington”
    “Harlem Blues”, Arranged by Sy Oliver
    “I’m Gettin’ Sentimental over You”, Lyrics by Ned Washington, Music by George Bassman
    “In the Still of the Night”, by Cole Porter, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Indian Love Call”, Words by Otto Harbach & Oscar Hammerstein II, Music by Rudolf Friml, for Piano
    “It Could Happen to You”, Words by Johnny Burke, Music by James Van Heusen
    “Jazz Combo Series”, by Roger Pemberton
    “Jazz Riffs”, by Charley Gerard
    “Jewish Song Hits”, for Piano, by Joseph M. Estrella
    “Jewish Songs, Old & New”, for Piano, Vocal, & Guitar
    “Just Friends”, Lyric by Sam M. Lewis, Music by John Klenner
    “Just in Time”, Lyrics by Betty Comden & Adolph Green, Music by Jule Styne, for Piano/Vocal
    “Just the Way You Are”, by Billy Joel
    “I Let a Song Go Out of My Heart”, Words & Music by Duke Ellington, Irving Mills, Henry Nemo & John Redmond, for Vocal
    “Mambo-Land”, by Xavier Cugat
    “I May Be Wrong, But I Think You’re Wonderful!”, Lyric by Harry Ruskin, Music by Henry Sullivan
    “Mean to Me”, Words & Music by Roy Turk & Fred E. Ahlert
    “It Might As Well Be Spring”, by Rodgers & Hammerstein, for Piano/Vocal
    “Million Goes to Million”, Lyrics by Arnold Weinstein, Music by Francis Thorne, for Piano
    “Misirlou”, English Lyrics by S.K. Russell, Fred Wise & Milton Leeds, Spanish Lyrics by J. Pina, Title & Music by N. Roubanis
    “Misty”, Lyric by Johnny Burke, Music by Erroll Garner
    “Moon River”, Words by Henry Mercer, Music by Menry Mancini, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “My Heart Belongs to Daddy”, Words & Music by Cole Porter, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “My Ideal”, Words & Music by Leo Robin, Newell Chase, & Richard A. Whiting
    “My Yiddishe Momme”, Lyrics by Jack Yellen, Music by Jack Yellen & Lew Pollack
    “Nothin’ But Blues”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “The Old Feeling”, Words & Music by Lew brown & Sammy Fain
    “One Dozen Standards”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “One Note Samba”, Music by Antonio Carlos Jobim, Words by Newton Mendonca
    “Paramount on Parade Band Book”, Arranged by John Warrington
    “Picnic on the Marne”, by Ned Rorem
    “Ramona”, Lyric by Wolfe Gilbert, Music by Mabel Wayne
    “Red Hot Mamma”, by Gilbert Wells, Bud Cooper & Fred Rose
    “’Round Midnight: Timeless Jazz Classics”, by Jamey Aebersold
    “Sam, You Made the Pants Too Long”, by Sam M. Lewis, Victor Young, Fred Whitehouse, & Milton Berle
    “Slightly Out of Tune”, English Lyric by Jon Hendricks & Jesse Cavanaugh, Original Text by Newton Mendonca, Music by Antonio Carlos Jobim
    “Softly, As In a Morning Sunrise”, Words by Oscar Hammerstein II, Music by Sigmund Romberg
    “Song of Black Max (As Told by the de Kooning Boys)”, Poem by Arnold Weinstein, Music by William Bolcom
    “Sophisticated Lady”, Words & Music by Duke Ellington, Irving Mills & Mitchell Paris
    “Star Dust”, Words by Mitchell Parish, Music by Hoagy Carmichael
    “Still More Songs of the Thirties” (Hal Leonard Corporation), for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Stormy Weather (Keeps Rainin’ All the Time)”, Lyrics by Ted Koehler, Music by Harold Arlen, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    Stormy Weather (Keeps Rainin’ All the Time)”, Lyrics by Ted Koehler, Music by Harold Arlen, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “Strange Enchantment”, Words by Frank Loesser, Music by Frederick Hollander
    “Stranger in Paradise”, Words & Music by Robert Wright & George Forrest
    “Swingin’ On Lennox Avenue”, by William Johnson, Arranged by William I. Rhoads
    “’Tain’t What You Do”, by Sid Oliver & James Young, arranged by Luther Henderson
    “Tea for Two”, Words by Irving Caesar, Music by Vincent Youmans
    “Tenderly”, Lyric by Jack Lawrence, Music by Walter Gross
    “Theater Songs”, Volume I, Words by Arnold Weinstein, Music by Willam Bolcom, for Medium Voice & Piano
    “Theater Songs”, Volume II, Words by Arnold Weinstein, Music by Willam Bolcom, for Medium Voice & Piano
    “These Foolish Things Remind Me of You”, Words by Holt Marvell, Music by Jack Strachey & Harry Link
    “This Love of Mine”, Words by Frank Sinatra, Music by Sol Parker & Henry Sanicola
    “Those Were the Days”, by Gene Raskin
    “Tiger Rag (Hold That Tiger)”, Lyric by Harry DeCosta, Music by Original Dixieland Jazz Band
    “Tom Jobim”, Volume 1, Produced by Almir Chediak
    “Tom Jobim”, Volume 2, Produced by Almir Chediak
    “Too Marvelous for Words”, Lyric by Johnny Mercer, Music by Richard A. Whiting
    “A Touch of Latin”, Arranged by Richard Bradley, for Organ Solos
    “Under Paris Skies”, English Words by Kim Gannon, French Words by Jean Drejac, Music by Hubert Giraud, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “The U.S. Air Force (The Wild Blue Yonder)”, by Robert Crawford, for Voice & Piano
    “Vocalise: Opus 34, No. 14”, by Rachmaninoff, for Cello & Piano
    “What a Diff’rence A Day Made”, Lyric by Stanley Adams, Music by Maria Greaver, for Piano/Vocal/Guitar
    “What’s New?” Lyric by Johnny Burke, Music by Bob Haggart, Performed by Linda Ronstadt
    “When You Wish Upon a Star”, Lyrics by Ned Washington, Music by Leigh Harline
    “When Your Heart’s On Fire, Smoke Gets in Your Eyes”, Lyrics by Otto Harbach, Music by Jerome Kern
    “A Whiter Shade of Pale”, Words & Music by Keith Reid & Gary Brooker
    “Who’s Sorry Now?”, Words by Bert Kalmar & Harry Ruby, Music by Ted Snyder, Performed by Marie Osmond
    “You & I”, Words by Isidor Lillian, Music by Abraham Ellstein, for Voice & Piano
    “You’ve Changed”, Music by Carl Fischer, Words by Bill Carey
  - "Psychedelic 60s", Climax Band Performance, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - Set Lists, 1987, undated (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - Sheet Music: Baritone Sax, 1982, undated (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - Sheet Music: Bass, undated (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - Sheet Music: Bass, undated (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - Sheet Music: Bass, undated (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - Sheet Music: Bass, undated (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - Sheet Music: Bass, undated (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - Sheet Music: "Book of Sing Sing Sing", undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music: "Climax, Piano, Red Book", undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Music: Drums, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music: East 13th Street Band, Bass, undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Music: East 13th Street Band, Piano, undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Sheet Music: East 13th Street Band, Working Music Manuscripts, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Sheet Music: Madrid Drums, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music: Madrid Piano, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Sheet Music: Madrid Tenor Sax, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Sheet Music: Misc., undated (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Sheet Music: "Moon of Alabama", undated (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Sheet Music: "Moon of Alabama", undated (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Sheet Music: Music Notebook, undated (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Sheet Music: "Nobody Home", undated (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Sheet Music: Piano, undated (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Sheet Music: Piano, undated (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, undated (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Sheet Music: Tenor Sax, White Book, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music: Trombone, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Music: Trumpet, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music: Trumpet, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Music: Trumpet, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Sheet Music: Trumpet, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Songs Book, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Songs Book, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Songs Book, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Administrative Files
  Series VIII: Administrative Files contains materials related to the operations of Larry Rivers’ Studio. These include memoranda, meeting minutes, documentation of conservation work and artwork photography, and collections of exhibition documentation for both Larry Rivers and other artists.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by folder title. Items within each folder are in their original order. Any titles inferred by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
  - Address Book, undated (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Files: A-F, 1985-1989 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Files: G-L, 1983-1989 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Files: M-P, 1985-1989 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Files: R-Z, 1977-1988 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Assets / Business Week, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1986-87, undated (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1987-88, undated (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1990 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - [Assistants' Files - Diana Molinari], 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - [Assistants' Files]: DM to AF, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - [Assistants' Files]: DM to AF, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - [Assistants' Files]: DM to AF, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - [Assistants' Files]: DM to AF, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - [Assistants' Files]: Selma Pending, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - [Assistants' Files]: Philip Farmer, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - [Assistants' Files]: SF Done, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - [Assistants' Notebook], 1994 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - [Autograph / Sketch Requests], 1986-2002 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Awards, Certificates, etc., 1979-89, undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Awards & Honors, 1964-99 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Benefits, 1995-1996 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Biographical Information, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Bios & PR, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Casual Labor & Commissions, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Completed To-Do Notes (1 of 2), 1985, undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Completed To-Do Notes (2 of 2), 1985, undated (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Computer Instructions, 1989, undated (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - [Directory], undated (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - [RESTRICTED] Disability Papers, 1985-88, undated (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Eastern Airlines Loss, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Employee Punch Cards, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Employee Records, 1995-98, undated (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1951-86, undated (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1963-2001, undated (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1964-95, undated (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1971-94, undated (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1972-97, undated (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1980-95, undated (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Federal Express, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Finished Stuff, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Finished Work Notes, 1988, undated (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Other Artists), 1963-2001, undated (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Other Artists), 1969-2001, undated (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Other Artists), 1972-97, undated (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1953-98, undated (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1961-99, undated (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1976-98, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Forget It, 1982-87, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Framing, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Framing / Conservation, 1990-1993 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Freelance Workers, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Statements, 1970-1986 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Gallery Transaction Notes, 80s-90s, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Grant Research, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Hampton Party List, undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Hogg Robinson of New York, Inc., 1995 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Image Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Image Requests, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Image Requests, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Info & Photo Requests, Donations, 1988-1989 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Info Requests, 1991-92, undated (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Insurance Claim: "The Narrow Circle", 1995 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Interviews (Requests, etc.), 1992-1999 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Invitation List for Marlborough Exhibition and Opening Party, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Invitations and Requests, 1976-2001, undated (Box 83, Folder 19)